<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
  <category>
    <id>c02</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>CA Web</title>
    <description>
      CA Web provides all the functionality of the existing The Concierge Assistant® application,
      with the addition of the ability to brand the application, ability to support multiple languages and character sets,
      ability to access multiple properties in the same brand.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>TCAweb.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>NULL</parentCategoryId>
  </category>
  
  <category>
    <id>c01</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Concierge Assistant</title>
    <description>
      The Concierge Assistant® is the single source for virtually all the
      information you need to communicate successfully with your guests or customers.
      It allows Guest Services, Sales, Housekeeping, AYS and other departments to share
      consistent, accurate information with a guest or other staff members in real time.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>TCA.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>NULL</parentCategoryId>
  </category>

  

  <category>
    <id>c03</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Voucher Assistant</title>
    <description>
      The Voucher Assistant is an Activity Desk voucher system that combines an elegant,
      intuitive user interface with powerful features for both Guest Services and Accounting staff.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>VA.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>NULL</parentCategoryId>
  </category>

  <category>
    <id>c11</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Features CA</title>
    <description>
      The Concierge Assistant® is the single source for virtually all the
      information you need to communicate successfully with your guests or customers.
      It allows Guest Services, Sales, Housekeeping, AYS and other departments to share
      consistent, accurate information with a guest or other staff members in real time.
      All communication barriers will be eliminated and it will not matter which shift,
      which day, who is off or who is working. When a guest asks about a request made,
      every staff member will be able to give them the correct status immediately.
      <![CDATA[<br /> <br />]]>
      CA provides the ability for any employee, anywhere in the world to assist guests with accurate
      and timely information enabling the guest to make only one inquiry.       It is Essential for
      all guest services enhancement programs. All documents presented to the guest, through either
      print or email format, can be presented with the property logo for a fast and professional presentation.
      It expedites the cycle time of each associate by efficiently locating both internal and external
      information for the guest.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>features.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c01</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>01</childItemId>
    <childItemId>02</childItemId>
    <childItemId>03</childItemId>
    <childItemId>04</childItemId>
    <childItemId>05</childItemId>
    <childItemId>06</childItemId>
    <childItemId>07</childItemId>
  </category>

  <category>
    <id>c12</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Integrations CA</title>
    <description>Gold Key Solutions is a member of the single itinerary group of the Hotel Technology Next Generation (HTNG).  Accordingly, we are proponents of Web Services technology to enable the exchange of information between various software applications at a property. </description>
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c01</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>08</childItemId>
    <childItemId>09</childItemId>
    <childItemId>10</childItemId>
    <childItemId>11</childItemId>
    <childItemId>12</childItemId>
  </category>

  <category>
    <id>c13</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Add-ons CA</title>
    <description>The Concierge Assistant comes loaded with a Google Maps integration for printing directions and with applications that provide service to other departments such as Lost and Found Items module, Rental and Inventory Module, Key Control Module </description>
    <imageUrl>addons.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c01</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>14</childItemId>
    <childItemId>15</childItemId>
    <childItemId>16</childItemId>
    <childItemId>17</childItemId>
  </category>

  <category>
    <id>c14</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Demo</title>
    <description>Request a live demonstration of our products.</description>
    <imageUrl>demo.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c01</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>18</childItemId>
  </category>
  <category>
    <id>c24</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Demo</title>
    <description>
      After providing us with your contact information you can view a video with the highlights
      of the application or schedule a live demo with one of our executives
      <![CDATA[
      <br /><br /><br />
      <p >
       <img class="arrow" src="images/arrow.gif" alt="" />
      <a href="DemoVideo.aspx">View a video demo</a> <br />
      <img class="arrow" src="images/arrow.gif" alt="" /> <a href="ContactDemo.aspx">Request a live demo</a> 
      
    
      ]]>
    
    </description>
    <imageUrl>demo.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c02</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>18</childItemId>
  </category>
  <category>
    <id>c21</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Features CA Web</title>
    <description>
      CA Web provides all the functionality of the existing The Concierge Assistant® application,
      with the addition of the ability to brand the application, ability to support multiple languages and character sets,
      ability to access multiple properties in the same brand.
      <![CDATA[<br /> <br />]]>
      CA Web provides the ability for any employee, anywhere on property to assist guests with accurate
      and timely information enabling the guest to make only one inquiry.       It is Essential for
      all guest services enhancement programs. All documents presented to the guest, through either
      print or email format, can be presented with the property logo for a fast and professional presentation.
      It expedites the cycle time of each associate by efficiently locating both internal and external
      information for the guest.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>features.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c02</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>20</childItemId>
    <childItemId>21</childItemId>
    <childItemId>22</childItemId>
    <childItemId>23</childItemId>
    <childItemId>25</childItemId>
    <childItemId>26</childItemId>
  </category>

  <category>
    <id>c22</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Integrations CA Web</title>
    <description>Gold Key Solutions is a member of the single itinerary group of the Hotel Technology Next Generation (HTNG).  Accordingly, we are proponents of Web Services technology to enable the exchange of information between various software applications at a property. </description>
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c02</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>08</childItemId>
    <childItemId>29</childItemId>
    <childItemId>10</childItemId>
    <childItemId>11</childItemId>
    <childItemId>12</childItemId>
  </category>

  <category>
    <id>c23</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Add-ons CA Web</title>
    <description>CA Web comes loaded with a Google Maps integration for printing directions.</description>
    <imageUrl>addons.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c02</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>14</childItemId>
  </category>
  
  <category>
    <id>c31</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Overview VA</title>
    <description>
      Gold Key Solutions designed The Voucher Assistant with Concierges and Accounting
      staff to be easy to use while providing the necessary features for managing all
      aspects of Activity Desk sales.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>VA.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c03</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>19</childItemId>

  </category>

  <category>
    <id>c34</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Demo</title>
    <description>Request a live demonstration of our products.</description>
    <imageUrl>demo.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <parentCategoryId>c03</parentCategoryId>
    <childItemId>18</childItemId>
  </category>


  <item>
    <id>01</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Logbook</title>
    <description>
      The Logbook
      Manager is the heart of the Concierge Assistant. This is where you will
      record all of your guest interactions. Each and every member of your
      staff will be able to answer questions with the same knowledge base. It
      is your digital journal allowing you to search for information in many ways: by
      name, by date, by room number, by profile, by concierge. Perhaps you wish to see
      only those entries that were created yesterday and today. Perhaps you wish to see
      only the Open items or just the Completed items. With the Concierge Assistant you
      may view your information your way.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>Book.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Logbook</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>Logbook</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>676</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>800</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Provide personalized and professionally customized confirmations and itineraries
      in PDF, RTF and Email formats that can be presented to your guests in up to 6 different languages.
      Locate all associated guest information by guest’s name, group association, “Guest ID” and many other ways.
      Every entry is date, time and initial stamped by the person who has performed the task.
      See “Today’s” activities color coded for a quick status check and avoid anything “falling between the cracks”.
      Make Dining Reservations online directly from The Concierge Assistant with our Open Table interface.
      Archive past requests/reservations for easy access on returning guests.
      Management reports and graphs for current as well as historical information.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>02</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Contacts</title>
    <description>
      The Contact Manager is the place to keep all of your contact information. This module Includes
      the integration with Google Maps to print directions and a Map. It is
      your digital telephone book (including the Yellow Pages). Each contact may be assigned
      to multiple categories (eg. French, Restaurant, Gourmet) allowing you to create
      a list of just those places you wish to review.
    </description>
    <!--<price>200.00</price>
    <inStock>true</inStock>-->
    <imageUrl>Contact.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Contacts</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Maintenance of your contact information is simple. You control what types of contact
      information you wish to have available. Telephone numbers (land lines and cellular),
      fax numbers, email addresses, websites can all be saved for the contact. When the
      next method of contact appears (maybe the Blackberry code) you will be able to add
      that to the list of available contact types. The Concierge Assistant is ready for
      the next technology.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>03</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Profiles</title>
    <description>
      The Patron Profile Manager is where you can create an individualized profile of your best guests.
      You can select by Last Name, First Name, State or by Profile Indicator with optional
      value selections.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>Profiles.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Profiles</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      You can create a Birthday Card list by selecting the Birthday Indicator and keying
      the month (eg. "Oct") in the Enter Value (opt) box.Patron Profile Maintenance is simple.The true power of this feature
      lies in your ability to define ANY profile indicators you wish.You will
      never outgrow this feature.If you wish to keep track of some new element
      simply add it to the list of available indicators. You even have the ability to
      add a "data entry hint" to assist your staff in entering the information in the
      correct format!
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>04</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Events</title>
    <description>
      The Event
      Manager is the place to keep all of your event information. It is your digital theatre,
      attraction, convention, concert and show guide. You control the categories of events.
      The Concierge Assistant
      gives you the ability to create a report of all events occurring during a guest's
      stay. They will be "Wowed" by your service!
    </description>
    <imageUrl>Events.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Events</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Select starting and ending event dates and print a customized list for your
      special guest. Perhaps your guest wants to know when Ricky Martin is performing or perhaps they
      wish to know how many conventions are in town this week.
      Maintenance of your event information is simple. You select how to categorize the
      event. Notes may be as extensive or as simple as you prefer.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>05</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Messages</title>
    <description>
      There are three sources of messages in the Concierge Assistant:
      Events, Logbook, and Text Messages.
      The Message Manager is where you can view the messages that you have received during
      your current session. This is also where you can create text messages.
      The Concierge Assistant checks for new messages
      constantly.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>Messages.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Messages</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      If you have more than 1 message the system will ask you if you
      wish to read your messages now.Event Messages give you all of the details
      of the event plus any additional message the sender may have added.
      Logbook Messages give you all of the details of the logbook entry.
      Free Form Messages contain whatever message the sender wishes to convey.
      There is no systemic limit on the amount of text you can send.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>06</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Administration</title>
    <description>
      The Administration
      Manager helps you to define how your Concierge Assistant will work. It is here that
      you select how you wish to categorize your information, who can access the information,
      how you want the information to appear.
    </description>
    <!--<price>600.00</price>
    <inStock>true</inStock>-->
    <imageUrl>Admin.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Administration</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      You have the ability to define the categories you wish to use for your Contacts,
      Events, Logbook Entries and Guest Profile Information.
      You also define your own Data Entry Panels to assure that your staff members will
      get the information you need.You define who on your staff has the ability to perform
      selected tasks.
    </functions>

  </item>

  <item>
    <id>07</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>CISP</title>
    <description>
      As of December 2006, The Concierge Assistant is a Visa CISP and PABP validated
      solution. CA uses Triple DES/AES methods to encrypt credit card information. As
      part of the Visa CISP validation.
    </description>
    <!--<price>700.00</price>
    <inStock>true</inStock>-->
    <imageUrl>Visa.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Visa</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      We provide all of our customers with 2 documents:
      1. Best Practices - Credit Card Encryption which can be used as a training document
      for your staff members, specifically for those that are authorized to de-encrypt
      the credit cards. And, 2. The CA Visa CISP Implementation Guide which gives a
      comprehensive overview of the CISP program as it relates to The Concierge Assistant.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>08</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>PMS Integration</title>
    <description>
      Gold Key Solutions can support Profile System (usually called CRM) Integration, a Folio Integration interface or
      both between our application, The Concierge Assistant (CA), and your PMS.
      We will be happy to work with your PMS vendor to accomplish this task.
    </description>
    <!--<price>700.00</price>
    <inStock>true</inStock>-->
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      In both cases the PMS or CRM are the repository for all guest profile information,
      CA accesses the PMS or CRM profiles on a read-only basis.  CA connects to the PMS or CRM via a Web Service,
      which is generally hosted on-property by the PMS vendor.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>09</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>OpenTable</title>
    <description>
      It is a two-way interface that assists the users in securing or canceling a reservation for a guest.
      This is a great time saver for both the property and the restaurants that the properties use,
      all without going to the web or making a phone call.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>OTDemo</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>676</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>800</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Confirmation Numbers are automatically assigned and if there is a cancellation it will automatically be routed to the restaurant.
    </functions>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>10</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Web Site Integration</title>
    <description>
      Your customer enters their requests into your website and through our interface, open logbook entries are created in CA. This process significantly improves guest services and efficiency by reducing the need to re-enter information, eliminating data entry errors and the possible loss of transactions.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>Web-IntDemo</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>689</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>796</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      When the Web Interface program completes the import of Profile and Logbook information a message is sent to the responsible concierge with a summary of all activity.
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />
    <p align="center"><img src="Images/Webinterface_675.gif" title="Touch Screen" Width="450" alt=""><br></p> ]]>
    </functions>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>11</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Touch Screen</title>
    <description>
      This integration basically makes all transactions through a touch screen from the customer's unit.
      It automatically creates a logbook entry in CA and notifies the Concierge through the messaging system,
      who can in turn confirm to the owner/guest once the request is completed.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      If the Concierge or Guest Services staff recommends a Restaurant or Service this is automatically updated in the Touch Screen.
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />
    <p align="center"><img src="Images/vertilincLive.gif" title="Touch Screen" Width="450" alt=""><br></p> ]]>
    </functions>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>12</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Activities Software Integration</title>
    <description>
      We interface with different activities vendors such as SpaSoft and ODS Limo (Transportation Company).
      These integrations are similar to The OpenTable Integration.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>SpaSoftIntegration</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>675</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>887</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      The staff of Gold Key Solutions has the technical and practical knowledge to increase the functionality of existing interfaces and to implement additional interfaces with other vendors or systems.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>14</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Google Maps Integration</title>
    <description>
      All Maps and directions are provided by Google Maps. You may also get reverse directions, walking directions, or directions in
      another language.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>addons.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>GoogleMaps</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>629</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>800</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>

    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>15</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Lost and Found</title>
    <description>
      In the Lost and Found application; items are entered and tagged for easy identification,
      with a photo of the item attached for a positive ID. The system records how and
      when items were disposed for tracking and reporting.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>addons.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>LostandFoundoverview</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>788</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>800</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      You can even link a picture of a Found Item!
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>16</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Key Control</title>
    <description>
      The Key Control system keeps keys and distribution to staff members organized very quickly and easily.
      This system will track each associate and key on property, with a record of check-out and check-in for each key.

    </description>
    <imageUrl>addons.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>KeyControl</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>577</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>720</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      The system allows easy addition of new keys and/or staff members, with comprehensive reporting available.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>17</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Rental And Inventory</title>
    <description>
      This feature comes included in all the versions of The Concierge Assistant and is ideal for departments
      such as Housekeeping to mantain their par-levels of controllable items as well as to manage inventory
      items such as roll-away beds, refrigerators, etc.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>addons.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>

    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>18</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Demo</title>
    <description>
      After providing us with your contact information you can view a video with the highlights
      of the application or schedule a live demo with one of our executives
      <![CDATA[
      <br /><br /><br />
      <p >
      <img class="arrow" src="images/arrow.gif" alt="" /> <a href="ContactDemo.aspx">Request a live demo</a> 
      <br />
     <img class="arrow" src="images/arrow.gif" alt="" />
      <a href="DemoVideo.aspx">View a video demo</a> 
      ]]>
      
    </description>
    <imageUrl>demo.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>

    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>19</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Voucher Assistant</title>
    <description>
      The Voucher Assistant is an Activity Desk voucher system that combines an elegant,
      intuitive user interface with powerful features for both Guest Services and Accounting staff.
      <![CDATA[<br /> <br />]]>
      Gold Key Solutions designed The Voucher Assistant with Concierges and Accounting
      staff to be easy to use while providing the necessary features for managing all
      aspects of Activity Desk sales.
      <![CDATA[<br /> <br />]]>
      The Voucher Assistant shares activity reservation data with The Concierge Assistant®.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>va.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl>Voucher Assistant</videoUrl>
    <videoHeight>735</videoHeight>
    <videoWidth>800</videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      <![CDATA[<br /> <br />
       <h4>
            Guest Services Features</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>Activity Inquiry module provides an organized directory to make finding and booking
                activities simple.</li>
            <li>Reporting system to show daily sales, un-issued vouchers and activity manifest.</li>
            <li>Activity reservation data shared with The Concierge Assistant.</li>
        </ul>
        <hr />
        <h4>
            Accounting Features</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>Accounts Payable module to manage vendor payments and assist with invoice and voucher
                reconciliation.</li>
            <li>Reporting system to query and show period sales.</li>
            <li>Net Due calculator to ensure proper set up of complex activities with multiple fees and taxes.</li>
        </ul>
        <hr />
        <h4>
            System Requirements</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>Microsoft Windows® 2000, XP, Vista.</li>
            <li>Microsoft .NET Framework 2.0.</li>
            <li>100 MB available hard disk space.</li>
        </ul>
      ]]>

    </functions>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>20</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>PCI-DSS</title>
    <description>
      Agoura Hills, CA. October 5, 2011. 
      Once again! CA Web has the attestation of PCI-DSS compliance and the report on compliance with all items marked "in place" as service provider level 1 as of October 5th, 2011. 
      A third party assessor used the PCI DSS Requirements and Security Assessment Procedures v1.2.1 to conduct this assessment. 
      The timeframe for this assessment was September 2011 – October 2011.
    </description>
    <!--<price>700.00</price>
    <inStock>true</inStock>-->
    <imageUrl>Visa.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Visa</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID></youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Since many guests of hotels use the concierge to make arrangements and reservations for them, 
      sometimes the credit card numbers and expiration date are required as part of the CA Web service. 
      The credit card numbers and expiration date are transmitted securely from customer’s browsers to the web application via SSL encryption and then stored, 
      encrypted in the database.
      <![CDATA[<br /> <br />]]>
      Gold Key’s CA Web does not process cardholder data and does not transmit cardholder data to any processor for processing.
      Gold Key stores cardholder data entered by the concierge at their discretion for convenient access by the concierge for fulfilling guest requests.
      All cardholder data is maintained internally to the CA Web (back-end database) only and is not transmitted outside the CA Web application.
      Gold Key Solutions does not serve any payment channel as they simply store cardholder data that their customers may enter into the
      CA Web application at their discretion. All cardholder data is maintained internally to the CA Web (back-end database)
      only and is not transmitted outside the CA Web application. Gold Key does not handle any chargeback or other card transactions or flows.
      Credit Cards stored in the Database are encrypted with 3DES 128-bit encryption.

      <![CDATA[<br /> <br />
      <b>At Gold Key Solutions, our customer's information security is our highest priority!</b>
      ]]>
      

    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>21</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Logbook</title>
    <description>
      The Logbook Manager is the heart of CA Web. This is where you will
      record all of your guest interactions. Each and every member of your
      staff will be able to answer questions with the same knowledge base. It
      is your digital journal allowing you to search for information in many ways: by
      name, by date, by room number, by profile, by concierge. Perhaps you wish to see
      only those entries that were created yesterday and today. Perhaps you wish to see
      only the Open items or just the Completed items. With CA Web you
      may view your information your way.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>Book.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Logbook</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID>sdzxzi1F7ss</youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Provide personalized and professionally customized confirmations and itineraries
      in PDF, RTF and Email formats that can be presented to your guests in up to 6 different languages.
      Locate all associated guest information by guest’s name, group association, “Guest ID” and many other ways.
      Every entry is date, time and initial stamped by the person who has performed the task.
      See “Today’s” activities color coded for a quick status check and avoid anything “falling between the cracks”.
      Make Dining Reservations online directly from The Concierge Assistant with our Open Table interface.
      Archive past requests/reservations for easy access on returning guests.
      Management reports and graphs for current as well as historical information.
    </functions>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>22</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Contacts</title>
    <description>
      The Contact Manager is the place to keep all of your contact information. This module Includes
      the integration with Google Maps to print directions and a Map. It is
      your digital telephone book (including the Yellow Pages). Each contact may be assigned
      to multiple categories (eg. French, Restaurant, Gourmet) allowing you to create
      a list of just those places you wish to review.
    </description>
    <!--<price>200.00</price>
    <inStock>true</inStock>-->
    <imageUrl>Contact.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Contacts</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID>dmWwhqeNstc</youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Maintenance of your contact information is simple. You control what types of contact
      information you wish to have available. Telephone numbers (land lines and cellular),
      fax numbers, email addresses, websites can all be saved for the contact. When the
      next method of contact appears (maybe the Blackberry code) you will be able to add
      that to the list of available contact types. The Concierge Assistant is ready for
      the next technology.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>23</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Profiles</title>
    <description>
      The Patron Profile Manager is where you can create an individualized profile of your best guests.
      You can select by Last Name, First Name, State or by Profile Indicator with optional
      value selections.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>Profiles.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Profiles</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID>MG-y7abCxQc</youTubeID>
    <functions>
      You can create a Birthday Card list by selecting the Birthday Indicator and keying
      the month (eg. "Oct") in the Enter Value (opt) box.Patron Profile Maintenance is simple.The true power of this feature
      lies in your ability to define ANY profile indicators you wish.You will
      never outgrow this feature.If you wish to keep track of some new element
      simply add it to the list of available indicators. You even have the ability to
      add a "data entry hint" to assist your staff in entering the information in the
      correct format!
    </functions>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>25</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Messages</title>
    <description>
      There are three sources of messages in the Concierge Assistant:
      Events, Logbook, and Text Messages.
      The Message Manager is where you can view the messages that you have received during
      your current session. This is also where you can create text messages.
      The Concierge Assistant checks for new messages
      constantly.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>Messages.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Messages</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID>vjEGoxeuc1M</youTubeID>
    <functions>
      If you have more than 1 message the system will ask you if you
      wish to read your messages now.Event Messages give you all of the details
      of the event plus any additional message the sender may have added.
      Logbook Messages give you all of the details of the logbook entry.
      Free Form Messages contain whatever message the sender wishes to convey.
      There is no systemic limit on the amount of text you can send.
    </functions>
  </item>

  <item>
    <id>26</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>Administration</title>
    <description>
      The Administration
      Manager helps you to define how your Concierge Assistant will work. It is here that
      you select how you wish to categorize your information, who can access the information,
      how you want the information to appear.
    </description>
    <!--<price>600.00</price>
    <inStock>true</inStock>-->
    <imageUrl>Admin.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Administration</imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID>KTo42pmJ6h4</youTubeID>
    <functions>
      You have the ability to define the categories you wish to use for your Contacts,
      Events, Logbook Entries and Guest Profile Information.
      You also define your own Data Entry Panels to assure that your staff members will
      get the information you need.You define who on your staff has the ability to perform
      selected tasks.
    </functions>

  </item>
  <item>
    <id>29</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>OpenTable</title>
    <description>
      It is a two-way interface that assists the users in securing or canceling a reservation for a guest.
      This is a great time saver for both the property and the restaurants that the properties use,
      all without going to the web or making a phone call.
    </description>
    <imageUrl>integrations.gif</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText></imageAltText>
    <videoUrl></videoUrl>
    <videoHeight></videoHeight>
    <videoWidth></videoWidth>
    <youTubeID>4F4Lbt7t-rg</youTubeID>
    <functions>
      Confirmation Numbers are automatically assigned and if there is a cancellation it will automatically be routed to the restaurant.
    </functions>
  </item>
</items>