<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<news>
  <!--
  *****Sample******
  <newsItem>
    <id>19</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Title
    </title>
    <date>2008-10-08T09:08:53.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Sub Title
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Article
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
    </content>
    <imageUrl>news2.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Gold Key Solutions - anim id est laborum</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>-->
  <newsItem>
    <id>27</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      GoConcierge.net Acquires Gold Key Solutions
    </title>
    <date>2012-12-12T12:12:12.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Client Base Expands to More Than 1,000 Hotels Worldwide
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      LOS ANGELES—December 10, 2012—<![CDATA[ <a href="http://www.goconcierge.net/home">GoConcierge.net</a>]]>, the Los Angeles-based provider of
GoConcierge, the lodging industry’s leading web-based task-tracking and database solution,
announced this week that it has acquired Gold Key Solutions, Agoura Hills, Calif. Like
GoConcierge.net, Gold Key Solutions is a provider of software solutions for concierge and other
hotel departments. Its Concierge Assistant applications are currently in 400 hotel locations
around the world. The acquisition means that GoConcierge.net will now expand its market base
to more than 1,000 hotel locations throughout the United States and more than 50 countries
around the world.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
“This acquisition will help us in our quest to deliver industry-leading solutions coupled with
exceptional support around the world,” says Adam Isrow, Executive Vice President of
GoConcierge.net. “We are very excited to have the Gold Key Solutions team join the
GoConcierge.net family. Together, they bring more than 35 years of lodging industry experience
and knowledge to GoConcierge.net and to our clients across the globe. We also welcome the
hundreds of Gold Key Solutions customers and look forward to working closely with them.”
“The Gold Key Solutions software development and client support staff is very excited to now
be working with the GoConcierge team,” says Newton Gore, president of Gold Key Solutions.
“We have had great respect over the years for the GoConcierge software products as well as their
customer service; clients of both companies will greatly benefit from this transaction.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
About GoConcierge.net:
      <![CDATA[<br />]]>
GoConcierge is a Web-based task-tracking and database solution for
concierges and other departments including guest services, front
desk, shipping and receiving, and restaurants. It is used by more than
500 hotels and businesses in more than 40 countries spanning five
continents around the world. Customers include properties from
major companies including Hilton, Hyatt, Fairmont, Mandarin
Oriental, JW Marriott, Omni Hotels, Peninsula, Le Meridien, Ritz-
Carlton, Rosewood, Raffles, St. Regis, Westin, W Hotels and Luxury Collection. For more
information about GoConcierge.net, go to www.goconcierge.net/home or call (818) 263-8993.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
About Gold Key Solutions:
      <![CDATA[<br />]]>
Gold Key Solutions’ The Concierge Assistant allows Guest Services, Sales, Housekeeping, AYS
and other departments to share consistent, accurate information with a guest or other staff
members in real time. The Concierge Assistant is a Windows based and web based solution that
offers two add-on programs: Voucher Assistant that prints vouchers for guests’ activities; and
Lost and Found which allows one to enter and tag items for easy identification.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
Contacts:
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
Adam Isrow, Executive Vice President
      <![CDATA[<br />]]>
GoConcierge.net
      <![CDATA[<br />]]>
(818) 263-8993 
      <![CDATA[<br />]]>
E-mail: adam@goconcierge.net
      <![CDATA[<br />]]>
www.goconcierge.net/home
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>

    </content>
    <imageUrl>goconciergelogoApril_2005.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Gold Key Solutions - GoConcierge.net</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
<newsItem>
    <id>26</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Concierge Assistant System Delivers Five-Star Resort Treatment to Hospital Patients 
    </title>
    <date>2008-10-08T09:08:53.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Winnie Palmer Hospital for Women and Babies Leads the Trend in Ultimate Patient Care
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Agoura Hills, CA February 11, 2010 
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	Having a baby is an emotional as well as physical experience and it should be a time when the mother and her family feel relaxed and cared for, especially in a new environment. Winnie Palmer Hospital for Women and Babies in Orlando, Florida understands this and made it their number one priority to provide parents and their babies with the utmost in personalized comfort and pampering. 	
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	  Five-star service for patients and families
In 2005 Orlando Health created a hospital concierge program for Winnie Palmer Hospital to provide a variety of nonclinical services to make a patients stay as comfortable as possible, which puts the hospital at the front of a very strong trend in patient care. Patient satisfaction is important in the healthcare industry because it ties directly to government funding
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	  Winnie Palmer Hospital had an overwhelming challenge to organize and prioritize its growing number of nonclinical patient requests for services, events, and information. In response, Orlando Health, which operates the hospital, hired Jenna Stallard as its customer relations manager to oversee what is today a very successful patient concierge program. Stallard was previously with Marriott Vacation Club International which uses The Concierge Assistant® a comprehensive hospitality concierge software system from Gold Key Solutions at all its properties to improve guest service. Based on her experience with Marriott, she recommended the hospital utilize it to streamline and standardize nonclinical patient services. 
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
"Our mission is to meet the nonclinical needs of our patients and provide them with a memorable experience via our comprehensive amenities program," Stallard said. "Hospital concierge service is a hot trend, and I am proud that our facility is a leader. We would not be able to provide our extensive suite of services without Concierge Assistant. It is at the heart of our department and program."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
The concierge staff of six at Winnie Palmer Hospital creates a warm, welcoming, five-star resort atmosphere for each patient. The 254-bed hospital offers services that include: 
	  <![CDATA[<br /><ul>
  <li>Upgraded in-room amenities</li>
  <li>Celebratory gourmet dinners</li>
  <li>In-room spa services for post-partum patients </li>
  <li>Complimentary movie rental</li>
</ul>]]>
	  <![CDATA[<br />]]>
Baby showers to go 
	  <![CDATA[<br />]]>
One of the staff's favorite examples of how they use Concierge Assistant is baby shower planning for women who entered the hospital earlier than planned and might have missed the fun of being showered with gifts for the baby from family and friends. With their concierge program, all of the information they need for the appropriate vendors is at their fingertips. This type of personal, warm interaction is what sets Winnie Palmer Hospital apart from other hospitals with similar medical offerings.
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	  "One couple called to request the exact same gourmet four-course meal to celebrate their most recent birth they shared after the birth of their first child," said Stallard. "Of course we record each patient's personal requests in our system so we could easily fulfill their request. We keep track of all preferences like spa services, favorite foods, and upgraded amenities to anticipate their needs and provide personal services."
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	  The hospital's professional concierge program gives patients an easily accessed central location to request services, instead of distracting the nursing staff from their duties. The time they give back to their clinical staff is invaluable to the hospital.
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	  "We put Concierge Assistant to work the day we started our training," said Stallard. "In addition to tracking patients' service requests, we use the reporting feature to track, trend and bill, which saves us a tremendous amount of time since we keep our service billing separate from the clinical system. We want our patients to leave Winnie Palmer Hospital with the best possible experience."
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	  Arnold Palmer Hospital for Children also recently implemented Concierge Assistant and they anticipate equally positive results in the coming years.
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>About Orlando Health</b>]]>
	   
	  <![CDATA[<br />]]>
Orlando Health is a $1.5 billion not-for-profit health care organization and a community-based network of nine hospitals and care centers in the Orlando region. The organization, which includes the area's only Level One Trauma Centers for adults and pediatrics, is a statutory teaching hospital system that offers both specialty and community hospitals. They are: Orlando Regional Medical Center; Arnold Palmer Hospital for Children; Winnie Palmer Hospital for Women and Babies; Lucerne Hospital; Dr. P. Phillips Hospital; South Seminole Hospital; South Lake Hospital (50 percent partnership); St. Cloud Regional Medical Center (20 percent partnership) and M. D. Anderson Cancer Center Orlando - the first affiliate of one of the nation's premier cancer centers The University of Texas M. D. Anderson Cancer Center in Houston. Orlando Health's areas of clinical excellence are heart and vascular, cancer care, neurosciences, surgery, pediatric cardiology and oncology, neonatology, and obstetrics and gynecology.
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
	  <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
    </content>
    <imageUrl>tN_0_EditWinniePalmer.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Arnold Palmer Hospital</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>25</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      SpaSoft® Announces Interface to
      Gold Key Solutions’ The Concierge Assistant® Software
    </title>
    <date>2009-11-16T09:00:00.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Implemented at Hotel Del Coronado
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      NEW HARTFORD, NY NOVEMBER 16, 2009 -- PAR Springer-Miller Systems, Inc. (PSMS) a wholly owned subsidiary of PAR Technology Corporation (NYSE:PTC) --- and the leading provider of guest-centric hospitality management systems --- announces the certification between SpaSoft Spa Management System Version 3.1.1 and Gold Key Solutions’ The Concierge Assistant using HTNG Standards/XML messaging  via SMS|Diplomat.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      <![CDATA[ <a href="ItemDetail.aspx?itemId=12">This interface</a>]]> between the SpaSoft Spa Management System and The Concierge Assistant system enhances guest service and improves the efficiency of your staff. Using HTNG Single Guest Itinerary messages, The Concierge Assistant system can display all activities booked in SpaSoft and add them to the guest’s Single Guest Itinerary.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “The SpaSoft <![CDATA[ <a href="ItemDetail.aspx?itemId=12">interface</a>]]> with The Concierge Assistant enables our office to run more efficiently,” said Eddie Rose, chief concierge at the Hotel Del Coronado.  “Each guest’s experience is enhanced and the interface streamlines our office processes.  We have used SpaSoft for two years and all our spa appointments are booked directly through the spa.  The interface between SpaSoft and The Concierge Assistant lets us access all our guests’ spa reservations without tying up the spa staff while we gather information.  This helps us run a much more professional operation.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “This leading edge <![CDATA[ <a href="ItemDetail.aspx?itemId=12">interface</a>]]> between SpaSoft and The Concierge Assistant enhances the guest experience and staff communications for properties immensely,” remarked Brigitte Diem-Guy, General Manager of SpaSoft Operations for PSMS. “The integration with The Concierge Assistant based on HTNG standards allows our clients to improve their efficiencies and focus on delivering superlative guest service.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      SpaSoft communicates guest spa appointments directly to the Concierge Assistant. Automated guest-activity tracking helps the concierge team run a more efficient operation and focus their attention on guest service.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “The Hotel del Coronado’s SpaSoft <![CDATA[ <a href="ItemDetail.aspx?itemId=12">interface</a>]]> with The Concierge Assistant improves guest service while enabling the property’s guest service staff to be more productive,” said Newton Gore, president of Gold Key Solutions.  “The real-time spa activity updates from SpaSoft to the Concierge Assistant enable The Del’s staff to provide guests with accurate itineraries any time during their stay.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About SpaSoft/PAR Springer-Miller Systems
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      An industry-standard for more than 15 years, SpaSoft is a fully integrated, dynamic activities management/scheduling software solution, specifically designed to meet the unique needs of the wellness and spa industry. SpaSoft's integrated offering includes resource management, activity scheduling, Web booking, group management, yield/revenue management and forecasting, Club membership, inventory management, PA DSS validated point-of-sale, business and financial reporting and analysis, as well as client management and history. SpaSoft is one of the many products offered by PAR Systems-Miller Systems Inc, the leading provider of hospitality management solutions. The extensive product line offered by PSMS meets the technology needs of all types of hospitality enterprises including city-center hotels, destination spa and golf properties, timeshare properties and casino resorts worldwide. For more information on PAR Springer-Miller Systems, visit our website at www.springermiller.com.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Hotel del Coronado
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The legendary Hotel del Coronado is located on 28 oceanfront acres on Coronado Island. Built in 1888 and designated a National Historic Landmark in 1977, The Del has played host to celebrities, presidents and dignitaries from around the world. Today, guests can select accommodations in the historic Victorian Building, in the contemporary Ocean Towers and California Cabanas, or in the new exclusive oceanfront cottages and villas at Beach Village. All together, there are 757 guest rooms, 28 suites, 70 junior suites and 78 Beach Village units.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Named the "best family beach destination in the U.S." by The Travel Channel, The Del offers endless recreation opportunities such as surfing, biking, boating, kids and teens programs.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Hotel del Coronado has several exciting enhancements recently opened including a world-class Spa, Beach Village and a state-of-the-art Fitness Center. The new Spa includes unique ocean-inspired treatments, hydrotherapy, relaxation areas for men and women and steam rooms. The cottages and villas at Beach Village include 78 exclusive ocean view guestrooms and suites, a private enclave with pools and hot tubs, front desk and concierge service, and access to all of the resort's amenities.
          </content>
    <imageUrl>SpaSoft.png</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>SpaSoft® 
</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>24</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Concierge Assistant Meets the Ultimate Guest
      Service Challenges of The World
    </title>
    <date>2009-08-18T09:11:50.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Five-Star luxury ‘Hotel on Water:’ residents of The World receive
      personal attention in hundreds of global ports
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Agoura Hills, CA - August 18, 2009 – When your clients are the crème de la crème, you cannot take risks with customer service — especially when your guests own the property. This is the case with The World, a 644-foot luxury residential ship with more than 120 owners of its elegant apartments.  The apartment owners enjoyed the floating lifestyle so much, they partnered to acquire the ship itself in 2003.   The ship continuously circumnavigates the globe with a staff of multi-lingual concierges that deliver personalized service to the most experienced travelers anywhere.  The primary challenge is finding and providing information on the best restaurants, shopping and entertainment in ports ranging from Hong Kong to Sydney, Barcelona, Bordeaux, Dublin, Rio and about 100 others.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      ResidenSea, which operates and manages The World, automated the ship’s complex guest services operation with The Concierge Assistant® a comprehensive hospitality concierge software system from Gold Key Solutions that is used by hundreds of exclusive luxury destinations and Five Star properties internationally.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The World is probably Gold Key’s most interesting implementation, but one that the Concierge Assistant (CA) handles with aplomb. “We think of ourselves as a five-star community at sea rather than a cruise ship,” said Ceci Leger, corporate concierge for ResidenSea, the Miramar, FL-based company that manages The World, a 12-deck vessel housing 165 private residences. “Our international multilingual concierge team uses CA to share guest request information with other appropriate staff.  This instantly enables us to fulfill the desires of our Residents and Guests professionally and quickly.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      The World is their oyster
      <![CDATA[</b><br />]]>
      To say that Resident Owners of a customized 12-deck ship are accustomed to a very high level of personal service is an understatement. “CA is a great tool because we have hundreds and hundreds of variables that our Resident Owners list as preferences,” said Leger. “These may be preferred transportation, currency, hobbies, flower preferences, and how they want their apartments prepared prior to their arrival.  We input these in our Concierge Assistant database for each Resident and update the information through regularly distributed questionnaires and onboard meetings.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Port information uploaded via satellite
      <![CDATA[</b><br />]]>
      The World’s staff provides detailed information on each port of call and CA enables them to tailor and deliver custom itineraries to each Resident based on their preferences. “This is a different concierge process than any other operation,” said Leger, who is a Les Clefs d’Or member and manages three on-board concierges from her shore-based office in Miramar. “I research each port of call in advance and upload my findings through our satellite link to the shipboard system daily to synchronize our databases. Gold Key created a Remote Contact Manager that enables me to export my findings instantaneously to the ship so Residents are up to date with the latest in-port events.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      What is your pleasure?
      <![CDATA[</b><br />]]>
      While arranging group activities is sufficient for the concierge team on a typical cruise ship, the Residents on The World have a different level of expectation. “We may provide a white-linen gourmet beach BBQ in the Seychelles for all Residents and Guests or a private dinner for two in an owner’s apartment.  Most of our owners prefer to make their own plans, and we honor their wishes and protect their privacy,” said Leger.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Service trend analysis
      <![CDATA[</b><br />]]>
      ResidenSea senior management values CA’s ability to provide an accurate picture of the “logbook activity” which clearly itemizes the service usage patterns as well as the amount of time being dedicated to the fulfillment of requests.  “We use this data in our quarterly activity reports to the ownership board,” according to Leger.  “It is an accurate reflection of the trends in our ship-board community, which among other things, makes it easier for us to identify where our attention should be focused to meet and, hopefully, anticipate the needs of our Residents and Guests.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      According to a long time Resident of this magnificent ship, “The real luxury is that at the end of every day, we are back in own private world.  Everything is provided to feel supremely comfortable aboard; a friendly and attentive staff, wonderful restaurants, great food; as well as tennis and swimming to keep us fit.  The World is a great community of like-minded friends.  All this, and the adventure of exploring and enjoying the whole world, without ever leaving the comfort of home… Pure Bliss.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><br /><b>]]>
      About ResidenSea
      <![CDATA[</b><br />]]>
      ResidenSea is a management company offering sales, marketing, operations and administration services for specialty luxury properties on land and sea. We believe in providing tailored solutions to ensure success.  We currently manage The World, the only private community at sea offering residential options and rental travel experiences to the discriminating traveler. Whether you are interested in purchasing a residence or renting a private home onboard  <![CDATA[<a href='http://www.aboardtheworld.com/' Target="_blank">The World</a>]]>, we are eager to assist you. If you would like to learn more about The World, please click here now. For additional information about ResidenSea (the management company), please contact us.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsWorldHongKong.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>The World in Hong Kong</imageAltText>
  </newsItem> 
  <newsItem>
    <id>23</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Gold Key Solutions Launches Web-based Concierge Assistant
    </title>
    <date>2008-06-19T11:27:03.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>CA Web enables brands to boost guest service across multiple properties, gather preference information to drive more effective marketing
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Agoura Hills, CA (PRWEB) June 19, 2009 -- Gold Key Solutions, developers of The Concierge Assistant® hotel system software announced the launch of its Web-based Concierge Assistant guest service solution, <![CDATA[<a href="Products.aspx?catId=c02">CA Web</a>]]>, that puts the industry's leading concierge software system on a secure, online .NET delivery platform. The system is accessed from popular browsers including Internet Explorer, Mozilla and others. The Concierge Assistant is used by over 400 full-service Ritz-Carlton, Marriott, Hyatt, Starwood, St. Regis, Four Seasons and other quality properties.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      <![CDATA[<a href="Products.aspx?catId=c02">CA Web</a>]]> is ideal for properties and hotel groups that want a browser-based professional concierge solution with all the functionality and benefits of the industry's leading property-based version. The new system is developed on the latest Ajax technology for online applications to deliver fast response times for more professional guest service that saves guests time and requires no additional hardware investment. CA Web enables hotel groups to access and consolidate guest-preference data via the Internet for brand-wide personalized service, more profitable marketing programs and its data may be seamlessly integrated with corporate CRM systems. The Concierge Assistant and CA Web systems are fully PCI-compliant to provide top-level security for concierge-initiated credit card transactions such as car rentals or activity purchase requests.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      "We developed <![CDATA[<a href="Products.aspx?catId=c02">CA Web</a>]]> for properties and hotel groups that wanted the option of using a secure Web-based Concierge Assistant system," said Newton Gore, president of Gold Key Solutions. "CA Web can gather information on what guests buy, where they go for dining, the transportation they prefer, what they do for fun, and transfer it to a corporate database for reporting and a greater overall awareness of guest spending and how to anticipate their needs - regardless of the property where they stay."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Concierge Assistant (CA) is a software solution that provides virtually all the information a property or hotel group needs to communicate professionally with guests, customers and staff. The system is designed to provide essential processes for all guest service operations with functionality proven in actual use at the world's most prestigious hotels. It enables guest services, sales, housekeeping, front desk and other departments to share consistent, accurate information with guests or staff members in real time. The Concierge Assistant allows instant cross-property communication regardless of time of day or location. When guests ask about their request, every staff member is able to give them the correct status immediately.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Gold Key also provides Voucher Assistant, a software solution that produces printed vouchers for guests' activities, provides an organized directory to make finding and booking activities efficient, and offers a comprehensive reporting system that covers all voucher sales and accounting requirements. CA's Lost And Found module provides the perfect solution for those hard to track items. Lost items are entered and tagged for easy identification, with a photo of the item attached for a fast, positive identification. The system also records how and when items were disposed for tracking and reporting.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The launch of Gold Key's new <![CDATA[<a href="Products.aspx?catId=c02">CA Web</a>]]> gives operators a powerful tool for concierge services that requires only a standard Web browser to utilize all effective innovations of the industry's leading guest service system.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>CAwebNews.png</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Gold Key Solutions Logo</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>22</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Five Diamond Venetian Resort-Hotel-Casino in Las Vegas
      Romances Guests with High Tech Concierge System
    </title>
    <date>2009-04-02T15:41:17.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>The Concierge Assistant Streamlines Stellar Customer Service for Ultra Luxury Resort
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      April 2009 – Whether floating down the indoor canal in a gondola, relaxing under the skilled hands of a professional masseuse, or shopping at one of the many luxurious boutiques, it is easy to understand why the luxurious Venetian Resort-Hotel-Casino in Las Vegas earned AAA's coveted Five Diamond Award.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Venetian's lush and romantic guest experience begins when guests enter the majestic entry way and enter a property that faithfully recreates the historic look and feel of Venice, Italy…with a Las Vegas cachet. Guests stroll down cobblestone streets under soaring frescoed ceilings, ride in authentic gondolas on The Venetian’s Grand Canal, and stop to feast in one of the 18 world-renowned restaurants, five of which have James Beard Award-winning chefs. The hotel offers more than 4,000 suites that are among the most spacious in the city with rooms drenched in opulence, furnished with plush beds and marbled bathrooms that include decadent, deep-soaking Roman bathtubs.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Service is the differentiator in 2009, and The Venetian’s elegance and sophistication includes superb customer service that is the hallmark of the property's Five Diamond status.  The Concierge Services team at The Venetian plays a most important role in each guest's visit. Whether stocking a returning guest's refrigerator with his or her favorite beverage or arranging a romantic rose-petal bath with truffles and champagne, the Concierge Services staff of more than 70 ensures a special experience. This is a remarkable feat to accomplish in a resort as big and busy as The Venetian.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      "We provide the largest concierge staff in the US and operate six full-service Concierge Desks within the lobbies of our properties,” says executive director of Concierge Services Tyra Bell-Holland.  “We pride ourselves on our discretion, professionalism and knowledge of what our property and city can offer to make every visit a special experience. Our goal is to provide guests everything they require and some things they did not even know they needed." Coordinating the duties of a team this size was a challenge, Bell-Holland noted, until they automated the property’s guest service operation with The Concierge Assistant® system from Gold Key Solutions, a comprehensive hospitality concierge software solution.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “Concierge Assistant centralizes all guest service tasks and other operational information onto one specialized system so our team operates more efficiently to deliver services,” Bell-Holland said.  “Every department in the hotel with password authority can access the secured information on area resources, reservations, and contacts, quickly enabling them to fulfill a customer's need.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Concierge Assistant plays a part in nearly every exchange between The Venetian’s property staff and its guests. For example, a bride was in a panic and needed a last minute alteration on her wedding dress the night before the wedding. The Concierge team used the system’s services database to find a seamstress that worked all night and the next day the bride had the wedding of her dreams in her custom tailored wedding dress that fit her like a glove.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      "The Concierge Assistant software is our 'bible' for managing guests at a mega-resort," says Bell-Holland. "The system enables us to provide a seamless guest experience at a moment’s notice."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Venetian's preferred car provider, ODS Limousine, receives more than 50 requests daily for guest transportation from the property’s Concierge team. Concierge Assistant electronically links The Venetian’s concierge team with ODS to streamline the delivery process. Payment information and reservation details are communicated instantly, saving time and minimizing potential mistakes.  The two-way communications between the limo company and the hotel makes it possible for guests to receive their transportation much more efficiently, which in turn, says B.J. Balaban, president of ODS Limousine, increases guest satisfaction.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      With a common vision for service excellence, Gold Key Solutions and The Venetian have created a formula for continued guest service successes.  "I cannot imagine being able to provide the world class service that we do so effortlessly without the support and guidance of Gold Key Solutions and Concierge Assistant," says Bell-Holland, laughing, "I prefer not to imagine life without it!"
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Venetian
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The Venetian Resort-Hotel-Casino, the largest property in the country to receive AAA’s Five Diamond Award and Mobil Four-Star, is one of the world’s most luxurious resort and convention destinations. Re-creating Venice’s legendary landmarks, the resort offers unmatched service and quality for leisure and corporate guests. Located in the heart of the Las Vegas Strip, The Venetian features The Grand Canal Shoppes, an indoor streetscape complete with gondolas and singing gondoliers, the Canyon Ranch SpaClub, world-class gaming, exquisite restaurants, and a wide variety of entertainment such as Phantom-The Las Vegas Spectacular, Blue Man Group, Wayne Brady and David Spade on its premises, as well as extensive convention and corporate services. For additional information, visit The Venetian website at www.venetian.com.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsVenetian-Moonshot.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>The Venetian Moon Shoot</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>21</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      New Caribbean Luxury Destination Reaches for the Stars with High-Touch Service
    </title>
    <date>2008-12-10T09:48:32.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Beachfront Resort Implements Concierge Assistant to Supercharge Guest Care
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Agoura Hills, CA December 10, 2008 -- With its prime oceanfront location on Providenciales in the Turks and Caicos Islands, the six-month old Seven Stars Resort is already making a name for itself as a luxurious Caribbean getaway, and not just because of its serene vistas of white sand beaches and crystal-clear blue waters. Built new from the ground up, the condominium-resort offers owners and guests a choice of two, three and four bedroom accommodations with elegant marble floors, sweeping balconies and a five-star attitude about "service excellence."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      "We are so new we have not been rated yet," said Seven Stars Concierge Services Manager Meghann Hussey, "But we are implementing guest service standards and creating a unique brand to achieve the highest possible rating. Our focus on extraordinary service will lead us there." Hussey, who traded in the white powder snow of Whistler Resort in British Columbia for the white sands of the Caribbean at Seven Stars, noted her first order of business was to implement a hospitality software package that would enable her and her staff of five to focus on exceeding guest requests instead of paperwork.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Customization Capabilities Supercharge Service
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      After evaluating many guest service packages, Hussey says she was "blown away" by Concierge Assistant® (CA) from Gold Key Solutions. "The system's customization capabilities were extremely important to me. Being on an island, there are many reasons why we need to create specialized processes and guest services, including specialized map-questing capabilities because there are no road signs here. With Concierge Assistant, I can easily do this myself without waiting for our company computer staff to build it for me." Hussey went on to note that refining the system to meet Seven Stars' specifications, including logos, professionally branded itineraries and owner/guest preferences, not only solidifies their brand and adds value to their destination, but supercharges their service focus as well.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      As a condominium-resort property, Hussey and her staff face the unique challenge of catering to the ongoing needs of owners as well as the changing preferences of each new resort guest. Hussey says CA is invaluable for working with owners by formalizing the resort's policy of 'active listening.' "We always listen with a 'second ear' to what our owners are saying. Anything that is relevant, like birthdays, anniversaries, or wine preferences, we capture and record in Concierge Assistant's Profiles section, because anything we can do for guests behind the scenes delivers an element of real service."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Save Time and Sanity
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The Seven Stars concierge staff also applies its process of active listening when making reservations for guests, especially wedding groups and other special event bookings. "Concierge Assistant has a groups module that enables us to itemize details in customized itineraries for group members. I rarely have time to update every detail of a wedding; thankfully, CA enables me to input the information in its database for timed follow up reminders," Hussey said. "It saves me so much time. I can review the details of an event and oversee deliverables in five minutes. I was kissing my computer after the last wedding!"
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Hussey says she is a fan of keeping Concierge services separate from the Front Desk, but that it is imperative all the rooms division staff coordinate their efforts to serve guests. The Concierge Assistant system allows the Seven Stars team to do just that. From anywhere on the property anyone with secured password access to the system can check the status of a guest/owner request or make recommendations on restaurants, signature dishes or other activities. Hussey likes to say her team delivers 'value-added concierge services' because of its computer-supported ability to seamlessly weave in maintenance and housekeeping needs while eliminating post-it notes, binders and other manual procedures.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      "The system streamlines our processes and keeps us all connected to better serve our guests and owners," she said. "I know the system is working because I get very few calls on my days off since we installed the Concierge Assistant. That means the property is running smoothly."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About Seven Stars Resort:
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Luxurious accommodations and attentive, yet unobtrusive, service are the hallmarks of Seven Stars which officially opened July 2008. Located on 22 beachfront acres of famed powder white twelve-mile Grace Bay Beach, the 115 residential units break out to 165 luxurious accommodations housed in three buildings. Courtyards, fountains and lush tropical gardens give way to magnificent ocean views. Two restaurants, a swimming pool, tennis courts, a spa/fitness facility and a play area for children are among the resort's features. The hotel's name comes from the seven stars of the Pleiades, the storied constellation seen so clearly from the Turks and Caicos Islands. In Greek mythology the stars represent the seven daughters of the god Atlas and goddess Pleione.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsSevenStars.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Seven Stars</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>20</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      100-Year Commitment to Impeccable Service Keeps
      the Legend Alive at The Grove Park Inn
    </title>
    <date>2008-10-08T09:08:53.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>The Concierge Assistant system enables historic property to
      meet 21st century guest expectations; contributes to a
      97% guest satisfaction rate
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      October 2008 – With a guest list that includes eight presidents, F. Scott Fitzgerald and Thomas Edison in its nearly 100 years of operation, The Grove Park Inn’s legendary status is well-deserved. And with solid growth over the past 10 years, many recent awards and a continued investment in flawless service, the legend is not only living, but perhaps just entering its prime.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “At the Grove Park Inn, our vision is to fulfill our legacy as one of America’s truly legendary resorts,” said Front Office Manager Oscar Alvarez. “Personalized service is a key part of the equation. Every staff member is dedicated to delivering the Grove Park Inn experience to each guest, to view every guest request as special and to ensure everything required of them gets done. This is the meaning of our mantra, ‘Everything We Do Matters.’”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Consistent satisfaction ratings over 97%
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Last year, The Grove Park Inn implemented the Concierge Assistant® system from Gold Key Solutions, a comprehensive hospitality concierge software solution, throughout the hotel to standardize its service and support its unique culture of superlatives. The results are impressive. According to Alvarez, monthly guest satisfaction ratings in the eight months since implementation have been consistently topped 97%, surpassing the property’s 95% standard.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “We are providing better service because we have better, faster, more effective communication between departments with The Concierge Assistant,” said Alvarez  “All guest requests are logged in our property-wide system that up-levels them according to how long they are pending,” said Alvarez. “Every appropriate staff member with password authority can quickly verify and respond to requests. For example, when a guest asks a concierge for limo service, the bell stand is alerted and can easily look up the guest’s arrival and departure information to schedule the limo without searching through countless e-mails.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Grove Park Inn, in Asheville, North Carolina, is one of the most sought-after destinations in the South. With a AAA Four-Diamond rating, the Historic Hotels of America property offers:
      <![CDATA[<ul><li>]]>
      512 guest rooms and suites<![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Many fine dining establishments <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      A Donald Ross-designed championship golf course <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      An award-winning, $42 million spa<![CDATA[</li></ul>]]>
      <![CDATA[<br /><b>]]>
      Staying ahead of the game
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Alvarez also appreciates how the system supports more personalized guest itineraries by matching them to guest profiles and printing them on Grove Park Inn stationary. “For example, if guests are going to the arts and crafts show in Weaverville, the system reminds us of their dining preferences and suggests options in the area that they might enjoy. Guests can plan their whole day around our recommendation or return to the hotel for dinner.  In either event, they are always impressed that we anticipated their requests.”
      <![CDATA[<br />]]>
      Other advantages of the system:
      <![CDATA[<ul><li>]]>
      A faster more professional guest service process thanks to automated accurate information on local locations, events, restaurants, etc.
      <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Consolidated information about the best golf courses and other venues in Asheville, as well as Yellow Pages, Rolodex information and Internet links;
      <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Professional-looking guest itineraries printed automatically with directions and contact information.
      <![CDATA[</li></ul>]]>
      Alvarez also said his staff is happier at their positions because The Concierge Assistant helps them do a better job.  “There is so much information available on events in the Asheville region, it used to take forever for our team to put together an itinerary,” explained Alvarez. “Now a wealth of information is at our finger tips and guests tell us they are amazed at how quickly we are able to meet their needs.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Grove Park Inn
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The Grove Park Inn Resort <![CDATA[&]]> Spa is one of the South's most venerable and famous grand resorts. Built in 1913 from granite stones mined from Sunset Mountain, the resort overlooks the Asheville skyline and provides guests with majestic views of the legendary Blue Ridge Mountains.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsGroveParkInnExterior.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Grove Park Inn Exterior</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>19</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      A 120-Year History of Service to the Stars Sets the Scene
      for Tradition at San Diego’s famed Hotel del Coronado
    </title>
    <date>2008-06-09T08:17:06.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>21st century technology helps put to rest the ghosts of service past
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Agoura Hills, CA – June 9, 2008 – With its rich history, exclusive island location, fabled guest roster and unparalleled service, the Hotel del Coronado is hailed as one of the world’s top resorts – for good reason.  Built in 1888, its original structure rises picturesquely out of the sand with the Pacific Ocean adding a spectacular backdrop to its landmark Victorian-style façade.  Catering to leisure and business travelers, the Hotel del Coronado has nearly 800 rooms and more than 65,000 square feet of high-tech meeting space.  The San Diego, California resort has played host to kings, presidents, celebrities, and even a ghost or two.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      ‘The Del,’ as its friends call it, receives rave reviews in travel, business and bride magazines, upholding its 120-year tradition of outstanding service.  More than 200 of its 1,100 member staff have been with the hotel for 15 years or longer and two members have achieved the remarkable milestone of over 50 consecutive years on staff.  It is that kind of dedication that The Del’s thousands of guests each week have come to expect.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Service Traditions with a Modern Twist
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      According to Chef Concierge Eddie Rose, the hotel’s focus on guest service is also the reason the resort maintains a year-round, full-time concierge staff of 10, with five more added during the busy summer season.  On any given day, Rose says, there are seven concierges available to immediately respond to guests’ requests, which can range from the sublime (purchasing Rolex watches) to the unusual (delivering ‘singing chicken’ telegrams).  When they are not actively engaged in providing concierge services, they are staffing three desks in the hotel lobby for easier access by both the hotel’s guests and the numerous tourists who wander through the property each day.  This unique twist on the familiar walk-up station is just one more example of The Del’s creative commitment to service.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Rose’s team also implemented The Concierge Assistant® (CA), an easy-to-use software program from Gold Key Solutions that automates the information-rich aspects of their highly personalized service.  “We use CA to keep us on track and create much greater efficiencies within our organization,” Rose said.  “The system enables us to provide better, quicker guest service so requests are answered professionally and on time.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      VIP Service ASAP
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Rose, who is responsible for all VIP and repeat guests, says CA is a great communications tool between staff, particularly when a concierge must pass along a guest request to another staff member because of a shift change.  The concierge assistant software tracks what has been done and alerts the other concierges about what is still required by the guest.  Additionally, the system allows Rose’s staff to track history on all prior guests so if someone asks for reservations at “that restaurant we enjoyed so much the last time we were here,” the staff can type in the guest’s name and immediately pull up the restaurant and the time and date the guest last dined there.  “It really impresses guests that we provide that scope of information for them in seconds.”
      <![CDATA[<ul>]]>
      There are many benefits to using CA, Rose notes, and tops the list with:
      <![CDATA[<li>]]>
      Instant Access to Information
      <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Guest information archives
      <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Guest profiling
      <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Organizational efficiencies
      <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Better staff communications
      <![CDATA[</li><li>]]>
      Provide detailed itineraries
      <![CDATA[</li></ul><br />]]>
      “When I started as Chef Concierge at The Del nine years ago, we did not have CA,” Rose said.  “We used to leaf through a stack of handwritten notes and had to decipher the often illegible writing.  The Concierge Assistant definitely makes us more efficient.  The less time we have to spend searching for information, the more we can dedicate to assisting our guests.  Time is money for most of our guests, and they want to spend their time on property focusing on their vacations or important business matters, not waiting for answers or service from us.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Using that same focus on service that launched the famed Hotel Del Coronado more than a century ago, Rose and staff are carrying on a storied tradition, but with a uniquely 21st Century twist.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Hotel del Coronado
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Rising from water's edge on the quaint Island of Coronado in San Diego, the Hotel del Coronado is considered one of America's most beautiful resorts.  A classic historic hotel, The Del was built in 1888 and designated a National Historic Landmark in 1977. Today, The Del offers travelers every contemporary convenience in an enchanting Victorian atmosphere. It is a combination that moved USA Today to call The Del "one of the top ten resorts in the world."  For those seeking a romantic getaway, The Del offers a quintessential Southern California resort experience. It's also the perfect family friendly vacation destination, offering abundant recreation options as well as seasonal teen and children's programs.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsHoteldelCoronado.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Hotel del Coronado</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>18</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Luxury and Service Make Life Different at
      The Residences at Two Liberty Place
    </title>
    <date>2007-11-15T17:00:53.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Staff utilizes The Concierge Assistant® software to deliver
      superlative service in a luxury environment
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      November 15, 2007 - The city of brotherly love is embracing a whole new concept of luxury living.  The Residences at Two Liberty Place, and its unique approach to city living in Philadelphia, has put this exclusive residence on the map.
      Housed in the third tallest building in the city, Two Liberty Place was completed in 1990, but the top twenty floors are currently being transformed into luxurious one-, two- and three-bedroom condominiums with jaw-dropping views that span three states.  It is more than the views that make The Residences at Two Liberty so unique, it is the service.  The upscale property instituted a ‘white glove’ five-diamond hotel approach to residential services that are implemented by a staff of concierges, a general manager,  assistant GM, and a bevy of drivers, doormen, condo messengers, engineers, and housekeepers all on 24-hour service standby and supported by a robust concierge software system named The Concierge Assistant (CA).
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      It really is different up there
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      According to Alex Cohen, general manager at The Residences at Two Liberty, the luxury hotel parallels are intentional.  “Our service is the property’s big differentiator,” he said.  “That is why we recruited our concierge staff from leading five-diamond hotels.  Their attention to the needs of our residents is amazing.”  And, the move from hotel to resident services provides the time necessary for the staff to really get to know the people they are assisting, Cohen points out.  “We are very proactive.  We conduct in-depth meetings with every owner, some lasting up to two hours, and gather as much information as possible to anticipate their needs.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The information is recorded in the property’s specialized hospitality concierge software from Gold Key Solutions that the staff uses to meet residents’ needs.  The system is based on property for greater data security and it enables the Two Liberty team to strengthen is personalized service by tracking:
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><ul><li>]]>Residents’ recreational activities<![CDATA[</li>]]>
      <![CDATA[<li>]]>Residents’ recreational activities<![CDATA[</li>]]>
      <![CDATA[<li>]]>Appointments<![CDATA[</li>]]>
      <![CDATA[<li>]]>Dining and entertainment preferences<![CDATA[</li>]]>
      <![CDATA[<li>]]>Favorite travel providers<![CDATA[</li>]]>
      <![CDATA[<li>]]>Special interests<![CDATA[</li></ul><br />]]>
      While the first residents will not actually arrive on property until spring 2008, the concierge staff is already hard at work.  Cohen says that purchasers can avail themselves of concierge services from the minute they sign a contract.  In fact, many have already received help with diverse requests such as shipping and storing a grand piano, finding a new pet, and booking a four-leg round-trip flight to New Zealand.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “Our Senior Concierge Jamie Cooperstein recommended The Concierge Assistant because of her experience using it at a prior five-diamond hotel employer,” Cohen said.  “She created numerous keyword links in the system to build a database of specific destinations and activities that enable us to fulfill residents’ requests very quickly.”  The Residences at Two Liberty Place also provides a “Virtual Concierge” communication system in every residence, enabling owners to make requests to the concierge through the touch of a screen.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Pets pampered with deluxe concierge service
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Two Liberty Place also caters to its four-legged residents, and will offer a deluxe VIP Pet Spa.  The Spa will offer pet walking, grooming and sitting services, all managed and coordinated with The Concierge Assistant, as will the many offerings also available in the fitness center.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      When completed, Two Liberty will feature a signature restaurant on the 37th floor that will be open to the public via a separate street level entrance.  Restaurant reservations will of course be a breeze.  “Concierge Assistant provides online reservation capabilities with all the restaurants in this area, including the one we will have here at Two Liberty Place,” said Cohen.  “A resident simply need ask and we can reserve their favorite table at their preferred time and even have their favorite beverage of choice chilling by the table.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      All that service sound impossible?  Not at Two Liberty Place, because life really is different up there.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Residences at Two Liberty Place
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The Residences at Two Liberty Place creates a paradise atop the Philadelphia skyline.  What was once just a landmark office building is now being converted into lavish one-, two- and three-bedroom condominiums with jaw-dropping views that span three states.  After occupancy begins in Spring 2008, owners will experience Five-Diamond service round-the-clock led by a team of hospitality professionals.  The goal is for owner’s to feel as if they are at a luxury hotel but never have to leave.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsTwoLibertyExterior.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Two Liberty Exterior</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>17</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      The Peabody Orlando, Four-Star, Four Diamond Service
      “Gold Key” to Success
    </title>
    <date>2007-10-08T09:08:53.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Anticipating guest needs is the hallmark of Peabody’s impressive service reputation
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Orlando, FL – October 17, 2007 – When it comes to service as a differentiator in the packed Orlando hospitality market, The Peabody Orlando, with 891 rooms and a gaggle of duck emissaries, knows how to be the best.  Since 1986, this popular business and leisure destination has turned individual guest services into an art form, anticipating everything from travel preferences like private planes and limousines to hypo-allergenic linen requests and specialized food requirements.  The innovative service even extends to the hotel’s daily entertainment, offering kid-friendly options like morning and evening red-carpet marches by The Peabody Ducks, world-famous for their twice-daily “march,” and story-time with Duck Master, David Robinson.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “Our goal is to deliver the ultimate in services so guests take a strong recommendation back home, and visit us often,” said Peabody guest service manager, Hameed Jasat.  “We fulfill many individual guest and group requests, from creating a romantic tented sanctuary with rose petals and champagne, to recommending local dining preferences and exotic transportation services that make a Peabody visit a sought after-experience.”  Speed and accuracy of service are the keys that make The Peabody Orlando the leader in their market, Jasat explained, but even more important is the staff’s ability to identify and provide the specific details that help to make a stay at the Peabody special.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Personal concierges for business traveler families
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The property’s Mobil Travel Guide Four Star, and AAA Four-Diamond ratings and service also extends to corporate groups.  The Peabody frequently assigns a personal concierge dedicated to assisting incoming groups and family members who accompany them.  When the property recently hosted a large pharmaceutical group, the Peabody’s personal concierge researched the interests of family members and created a children’s lollipop activity at the pool and offered poolside movies and popcorn in the evening.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Guest service software prints professional itineraries
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      One of the most important tools used by The Peabody Orlando to deliver its award-winning guest services is a specialized concierge software system.  Shunning old-fashioned ring binders that take time to use and often contain outdated information, the Peabody invested in The Concierge Assistant® system from Gold Key Solutions, a comprehensive, integrated solution that it installed on desktops throughout the hotel to standardize its service.  “The Concierge Assistant (CA) is a comprehensive software system we rely on,” Jasat said. “It enables us to instantly display current information on local attractions, stores, dining options, events, airlines, transportation companies – everything.  Plus, we can print personalized, professional itineraries and maps with phone numbers and activity schedules that have the Peabody’s logo and the concierge’s signature.”   One of The Concierge Assistant’s greatest benefits, Jasat noted, is its ability to quickly link to Open Table for dining reservations.  “With hundreds of dining options to choose from in Orlando, access to off-site restaurant availability and reservation booking is important to serving guests, and it is instantaneous using CA.  The system prints out driving directions, reservation times and contact information on the spot.  Our busy guests always value this because it saves them time. ”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      According to Jasat, The Peabody Orlando’s team of 55 guest services staff maintain their market leading position by never saying “no” to guests.  “We vigorously anticipate their needs and strive to exceed expectations,” he said.  “Additionally, we use The Concierge Assistant to track the requests of each of our guests as well as arrivals of all VIP guests.  The duck master calls each one before they arrive to either welcome them as first-time guests, or to welcome them back and offer to meet any needs once they are here.  All preferences and requests are recorded in CA and acted upon once they are on the property.”   It’s just one way, Jasat notes, that the Peabody continues to rise to the superior level it’s “quacked” up to be.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Peabody Orlando is a property of Peabody Hotels within the portfolio of Peabody Hotel Group, Memphis, Tennessee.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Peabody Orlando
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The Peabody Orlando is a custom-built, landmark hotel, catering to the meetings and conventions industry nationwide. The hotel is a masterpiece of contemporary design and luxurious décor and furnishings. Since opening its doors in 1986, The Peabody Orlando has established itself as the area’s multi award-winning convention hotel of choice for the nation's professional meeting planners.  It’s trademarked Peabody Service Excellence™ guarantees consistent, hotel-wide, first class service.  As one of only two Mobil Travel Guide Four-Star, AAA Four Diamond hotels in the entire city, the luxury accommodations match world-class lodging with a convenient setting.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsPeabodyOrdo.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>The Peabody Orlando Exterior</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>16</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Capella Hotels <![CDATA[&]]> Resorts Selects The Concierge Assistant ®
      Software for All Properties
    </title>
    <date>2007-06-18T09:08:53.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>New Ultra Luxury Chain uses Concierge Assistant system to support matchless service
      at Schloss Velden, a Capella Hotel
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      Agoura Hills, California – June 18, 2007 – Gold Key Solutions, developers of The Concierge Assistant® software system, announced it was selected by Capella Hotels <![CDATA[&]]> Resorts for use at all of the chain’s new ultra-luxury properties throughout the world.  Capella will use The Concierge Assistant hotel system software to standardize and streamline the highest quality guest service.  The chain’s first property, Schloss Velden, a Capella Hotel, opened in May 2007 and two more Capella openings are forecast before year-end,
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “Capella Hotels <![CDATA[&]]> Resorts is establishing a new benchmark for hospitality luxury and guest service,” said Scott Rohm, Senior Vice President of Operations for Capella.  “In addition to Capella’s spectacular locations, our team of Personal Assistants will be proactive in providing guests with every need during their stay.  Capella will use The Concierge Assistant software for all its properties to help it manage guest relationships, develop itineraries for guest scheduling for dining, spa and other services to give guests the most personalized attention.”  Rohm explained Capella is different from the usual luxury hotel in one key area.  It replaced the common public-area concierge position with professionally trained Personal Assistants that are positioned in each property’s well-appointed private sitting room, which is a comfortable area maintained exclusively for guests.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Newton Gore, President of Gold Key Solutions, said, “Today’s discerning guests expect more from a luxury property than in the past.  Capella recognizes this need and is addressing it with a balance of beautiful boutique hotels in stunning locations and highly personalized guest care.  The Concierge Assistant software is an ideal tool to support Capella’s goal to provide enriching experiences and superb service.”    The Concierge Assistant software is a server-based secure application that tracks trends in guest activities, appointments and requests and enhances customer service by automating tasks such as itinerary planning and printing, and special requests.  It is used by more than 300 luxury hotels around the world to enable more professional, personalized attention to guests.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Capella Hotels <![CDATA[&]]> Resorts promises unique benefits of the finest boutique hotels including elegant refined architecture and interior design, privacy, individualized service and attention to detail combined with the amenities of the world’s great luxury hotels and resorts. The Schloss Velden, a Capella Hotel, is a beautifully restored Austrian lakeside castle opened in May 2007 as the first Capella property.  The company is expected to open two more properties in 2007 and forecasts a total of seven hotels to be in service by the end of 2008.  Sites for future Capella Hotels <![CDATA[&]]> Resorts include Capella Castlemartyr in Ireland, Capella Pedregal in Cabo San Lucas, Mexico, Sentosa Island, Singapore and Telluride, Colorado.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Capella’s Scott Rohm said, “Our goal is to place Capella above the typical Five-Star level to deliver the ultimate quality experience to every guest.  The staff at each property will be carefully selected and completely familiar with the surroundings, activities and history of each hotel’s locale.  We are leveraging The Concierge Assistant to create personalized profiles of each guest to anticipate his or her needs to provide the finest in client care.  When it is used well, superior technology is the perfect complement to Capella’s unsurpassed service standards.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About Capella Hotels and Resorts
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Capella Hotels and Resorts serves today's top-tier travelers and residential property owners and is setting a new standard in the hospitality industry. Capella promises the unique benefits of the finest boutique hotels, including superb architecture and interior design, privacy, individualized service and attention to detail - combined with the amenities and activities of the world's great luxury hotels and resorts. Capella, led by founder Horst Schulze, is a brand focused on customer choice, and offers choices that no other hotel company in the world can match. Capella is opening world-class properties in cities and resort destinations around the world, including: Breidenbacher Hof, a Capella Hotel (Düsseldorf, Germany); Capella Castlemartyr (Cork, Ireland); Capella Pedregal (Cabo San Lucas, Mexico); Capella Singapore (Sentosa Island, Singapore); Capella Telluride (Telluride, Colorado); Capella Dunboy Castle (Cork, Ireland); and Schloss Velden, a Capella Hotel (Velden, Austria). Learn more at www.capellahotels.com.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsSchlossVeldenCapellaExteriorJune2007.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Schloss Velden Capella Exterior</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>04</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Luxury Marco Beach Ocean Resort Aims at 5th
      Diamond, Leverages The Concierge Assistant
    </title>
    <date>2005-06-13T09:48:32.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Guest services streamlined by tapping guest histories
      to anticipate individual tastes, delights visitors
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      June 13, 2005 - If you are flying to Southern Florida in your Gulfstream V executive jet and need a luxury 4-Diamond resort with an award winning chef and, by the way, a nearby airfield big enough to accommodate your plane, the Marco Beach Ocean Resort will probably be where you spend the night.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Marco Beach Ocean Resort is a 100-suite independent destination on Florida’s Marco Island built by the Gulf Bay Group of Companies to 5-Star, 5-Diamond standards. The property --with its own private Fiddler’s Creek golf club and deep-draft marina -- opened only eight months ago and already has one of the highest ratings Triple A grants and aims higher. Phillip Starling, Marco Beach Ocean Resort’s managing director, said, "We offer one of the most beautiful destinations in the world. With our entire management team experienced in operating luxury properties, our goal is to earn the AAA 5-Diamond designation soon as possible. At the top of the luxury market the differentiator is guest service; that is our focus. We stock guests’ rooms with their favorite foods and beverages, contact them before and after their stay, and track each person’s interests and activities in the property’s Concierge Assistant software system."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      "What attracted us to The Concierge Assistant was that it gives us power over our guest history information and puts that data to work in ways no property management system could," said Starling. "The guest profiles we build in our concierge system contain all past stay information, as well as their off-property transportation requests, favorite restaurants, and travel details. We could even include a digital photo of the guest in their file to boost guest recognition. This is a tool that lets us know what guests will want before they ask, and is a key tool as we work toward earning our fifth diamond."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Guest data is secured
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The property’s guest service team contacts guests prior to their arrival to help plan their visit and ensure their itinerary of events is known by the resort. "We log each guest’s activities in The Concierge Assistant software; already knowing what they enjoy lets us offer suggestions that are tailored to their unique preferences. The system runs on the property’s networked server so all appropriate staff members can access a guest’s data at anytime; this guarantees we can answer questions from any touch point in the resort. Also, since The Concierge Assistant is property-based we do not have to worry about hackers or identity theft over the Internet."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      To provide the utmost in convenience the Marco Beach Ocean Resort contracts with a luggage transport company that picks up guests’ luggage at their homes and ships it directly to the property, relieving visitors of delays associated with airport security. "Our goal is to provide guests with a stress-free travel experience," said Starling. "Our managers personally call each guest during their stay to judge the service they are receiving. Visitors tell us they relish being here more than at a larger flagged hotel because we make them feel important." The resort also uses a ‘cartless’ housekeeping service and staff that operates from centralized closets to eliminate clutter in hallways, just as their guest services software eliminates clutter at the concierge desk.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      One item at the top of most guest interest lists at the Marco Beach Ocean Resort is the property’s signature restaurant, Sale e Pepe. Featuring Northern Italian cuisine, its master chef, Alberto Varetto, who was featured at the James Beard Foundation, flies in ingredients directly from Italy to create a stunning dining experience. "Guests love Sale e Pepe and its 3,000-bottle wine cellar; which we just learned will be given an award in the August issue of Wine Spectator," explained Starling. The property also offers relaxed dining at the Gator Grill at its Fiddler’s Creek golf club, as well as waterfront dining at Backwater Nick’s at the private Isle of Capri Marina. "When guests first reserve with us we create a personal profile for them in The Concierge Assistant system that tracks their dining preferences, on property and off, as well as, favorite tee times, and individual spa treatments," Starling said. "We focus on customized service, name recognition and surpassing guest expectations. In addition to vacationing guests, we host many executive groups who value our high-tech meeting facilities and the wide variety of venues and activities we offer."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Marco Beach Ocean Resort provides meeting space for professional and social groups of up to 100 attendees and prides itself in delivering the highest quality working environment for visiting business people. To host large parties in style for special occasions the resort features its beautiful Gulf Ballroom on the beach facing the ocean. "Many groups prefer to fly directly in to Marco Island’s large private airfield, attend meetings, and play golf, take cruises, or fish after their business is wrapped up," said managing director Phillip Starling. "Some companies buy out one of our restaurants one evening, and then have other events offsite at Fiddler’s Creek or the marina on subsequent days. We provide limo service from our own company to maintain the highest service level and flexibility. Some luxury properties offer a ‘Club Level’ with special consideration for their highest-rated guests; we provide that level of service for all our guests."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      In a surprise move the property intentionally hired 60 percent of its line staff without previous hotel experience so the management team could train them to its own high standards for refined service and create an atmosphere of friendliness. The Concierge Assistant reinforces that care by automating most guest service activities and reporting, thus creating orderliness and accuracy throughout the concierge process, and greatly reducing report generation activity for management oversight. "We are using technology to standardize the highest quality of guest service," concluded Starling.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Marco Beach Ocean Resort
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Perfectly situated on the Gulf of Mexico, Marco Beach Ocean Resort opened in 2001 bringing world class service and exquisite dining to Southwest Florida. Rated 4-Diamonds by AAA, it is one of Florida’s most luxurious beach resorts and a member of Preferred Hotels and Resorts Worldwide. The all-suite independent hotel offers 84 luxurious one-bedroom and 15 elegant two-bedroom suites on the beach. All units are equipped with high thread-count European feather bedding, rich wood furnishings, kitchens, luxurious marble showers with separate bathtubs, and floor-to-ceiling glass doors. Spacious balconies from many suites command sweeping panoramic views of the blue green water of the Gulf of Mexico. A concierge is on duty 24 hours a day, and maid service is provided twice daily with turn down service. Guests are invited to enjoy the fitness facilities, personal fitness training, sauna and steam rooms, as well as an array of massages, body therapies and facials. Formal dining at the resort is truly a transporting experience. The recently opened Sale e Pepe restaurant transports guests to the ancient hills of Tuscany and the savory regions of the Southern Italy. The enchanting Toulouse Lounge enables guests to relax with cocktails and to dream about turn-of-the century Paris, while admiring the reproductions of this great French artist. Beachside and poolside bars are never far away dispensing cool refreshments.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsMarcoBeachResortPool2005.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Gold Key Solutions - anim id est laborum</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>03</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      LaPlaya Beach <![CDATA[&]]> Golf Resort Installs The Concierge
      Assistant Software, Redefines Service Standard
      for New Elite Club and 5-Star Guests
    </title>
    <date>2005-05-25T09:48:32.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>Software Lets Staff Track Luggage, Schedule
      Activities on the Fly for Five-Star guests
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      May 25, 2005 - LaPlaya Beach <![CDATA[&]]> Golf Resort, operated by Noble House Hotels, is a shining jewel on the white-sand beach of Naples, Florida.  The former mid-scale beach-front hotel recently emerged from a complete $54M makeover as much more than a hotel.  In addition to beautiful new resort facilities, the transformed LaPlaya now offers an exclusive 654-member club with its own private golf course, the elegant SpaTerre spa fitness center, and is attracting a new class of clientele accustomed to five star service.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      LaPlaya’s managing director, Scott Shoenberger, said, “LaPlaya has gone through a complete facility renovation and lifestyle upgrade.  We escalated from a three-star family property to an exclusive four-to-five star resort with private luxury club and golf course.  Our resort guests and club members have access to a world-class destination here and they expect the highest level of service and personalized attention during their stay.  Guest recognition and knowledge of client preferences have become essential to our new quality standards.”   To help its staff deliver first class service to its guests and members, LaPlaya installed the widely respected The Concierge Assistant Windows-based concierge software from Gold Key Solutions, throughout the property.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      “We wanted a system that would elevate our service by maintaining detailed profiles of each member and guest and track their activities and preferences on property and off,” said Shoenberger.  “We also wanted to give our staff a way to communicate guest needs throughout the resort. The Concierge Assistant software creates a profile with complete contact information and activity history for each guest, including the ability to display a digital photo to allow instant recognition.  The guest profile shows our staff when guests have stayed here before, if they prefer spa or golf, what restaurants they frequent and many other facts that let us serve clients more professionally.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Groups are a large part of LaPlaya’s business, and the property hosts many high-end corporate retreats, company gatherings and member-sponsored functions.  “We are finding that many planners want a luxury venue for their company meetings,” said LaPlaya’s Scott Shoenberger.  “With members hosting meetings the property is often filled and we must be prepared to serve 1,300 ultra-VIPs almost every day.  The Concierge Assistant system has made this much easier than before when we had to track everything manually.  The system even provides custom-printed itineraries with meeting times and function room locations for group members.”   Since so many activities are available, providing guests with personalized schedules for spa appointments, tee times and dinner reservations is also a welcome service.  “Image is a key part of high-quality guest service, and The Concierge Assistant creates attractive guest documents with the LaPlaya logo for a very professional appearance.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Data Security Insurance
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Security is also a priority for LaPlaya.  “We have members-only areas that are constantly monitored by staff in wireless communication with our offices,” said the LaPlaya’s managing director, Scott Shoenberger.  “Since we maintain a great deal of highly personal guest and member information in our files, data security is of primary importance to us.  We don’t have time to become experts in firewalls and Internet security, and our data is too valuable to take risks.  To ensure safety, none of our systems are open to the public Internet, which is the most frequent entry point for database penetration.  Our Concierge Assistant system, which houses much of our guest information, is secured on a property-based server inaccessible to hackers.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Whether guests come to LaPlaya for business or pleasure, they usually pack for a variety of activities such as fine dining, beach sports, golf and formal events.  At check-out time the array of luggage can cause a unique problem at the luxury resort.  “The way we handle lost and found items is important to our guests,” said Shoenberger.  “Not only must their valuables be adequately secured, but dated and tracked by room number and possible owner.  In the past we used our big red logbook, but this was an inefficient and error-prone way to track guest belongings.  Now our concierge software handles this duty efficiently and allows us to quickly notify guests of items they may have left behind. This is the kind of service our clients value.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The way a staff coordinates its activities and shares information about guest requests is critical to good service at any property.  LaPlaya automated this process as well.  Every workstation is connected to the property’s Concierge Assistant software system for instant, accountable cross-property communication.  “Guests often make verbal requests at the front desk or to other staffers to arrange tee times, spa appointments, dinner reservations or to schedule transportation,” said Scott Shoenberger.  “Our clientele trusts their requests are being addressed, and they expect confirmation their reservations are received by the appropriate outlet.  We automated the process through our concierge system to strengthen guest service.  When one of our staff receives a guest request, he or she enters it into The Concierge Assistant for action and it is instantly broadcast throughout the resort.  When the appropriate team member at SpaTerre, our golf course, or in one of our restaurants gets the message the system mandates they confirm receipt before it allows them to continue work.  This kind of technology supports our service standards by keeping our staff accountable.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The new LaPlaya Beach <![CDATA[&]]> Golf Resort is an oasis in Florida, with fishing, beach activities, a luxury spa and Bob Cupp-designed par 72 championship course it is attracting guests from around the world to the Naples Gulf Coast.  “As a true destination our guests and members expect us to be knowledgeable about the surrounding Florida area,” explained Shoenberger.  “We maintain a comprehensive listing of area restaurants, attractions and activities in our Concierge Assistant system.  The installation and training team from Gold Key Solutions had everything loaded in the system when it was delivered so we had a running start.  The Gold Key team’s extensive experience with the top four- and five-star properties in our class helped us understand innovative ways to use the system to assist our clients at every touchpoint.  Our business at LaPlaya is about pleasing guests; The Concierge Assistant system is a great tool for delivering service that exceeds guest expectations.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About Noble House Hotels La Playa
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Located on the beach, LaPlaya Beach <![CDATA[&]]> Golf Resort rests amidst the natural and legendary beauty of Naples in Southwest Florida. A true Florida beach resort known for its spectacular views, unforgettable sunsets and pure white sand, LaPlaya also features Naples waterfront dining with the acclaimed Baleen and SpaTerre - the most luxurious and pampering among Florida Spas. LaPlaya also offers the finest golfing facilities among Florida golf resorts.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsLaPlayaResortNobleFlorida.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Gold Key Solutions - anim id est laborum</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>02</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      Luciano Pavarotti, Laura Bush and Tom Hanks Make Appearances in The Rittenhouse Lobby
    </title>
    <date>2005-03-02T09:48:32.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>
      Philadelphia's Elegant Home to Diplomats and Celebrities
      Uses Concierge Software to Empower Staff, Deliver
      Oprah Winfrey's Dog Biscuits
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      March 2, 2005 - What did Oprah Winfrey find when she registered at Philadelphia's most famous Five-Diamond hotel? A basket of monogrammed dog biscuits imprinted with her pet's names, a hand written welcome letter from the general manager, and a refrigerator filled with her favorite foods were all waiting for Ms. Winfrey when she checked into her suite at The Rittenhouse.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      When staff discovered that a high-ranking diplomat visiting The Rittenhouse from Japan was an avid sports fan, the property cabled his favorite Japanese television network into his suite's entertainment center before he arrived. After being guided through the lobby of the same hotel on arrival, the Croatian prime minister, his ambassador to the US and their aids were greeted in their rooms by welcome letters in their own language. President Bill Clinton, President George Herbert Walker Bush, Prince Andrew, Laura Bush, Arnold Palmer and Tom Hanks among others have also been guests at The Rittenhouse.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      In addition to being the home away from home to a growing family of elite clientele The Rittenhouse has earned the AAA Five Diamond Award for 14 consecutive years and merited a position on the Conde Nast Gold List as one of the best places to stay in the world. David Benton, The Rittenhouse's vice president and general manager since 1990, explained that it takes more than a beautiful property and an attentive staff to be the hotel of choice for the most discerning travelers in politics and entertainment. "The key to success in our market is personalized service that honors each guest, and more importantly, the empowerment of each employee to provide it. We understand that each guest is unique with individual requirements, and we train our staff to be flexible." Benton noted that if a guest believes an error has been made in their billing or room assignment, every member of the front desk team has the authority to make corrections and satisfy the guest's needs instantly without a manager's approval.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      For many years The Rittenhouse tracked guest requests in triplicate with a proven paper-based method, but found the system was becoming inefficient as the volume of requests increased. "Last year our head concierge was impressed by a guest service software package named The Concierge Assistant. We installed the system and are pleased to say it has increased the amount of information we can provide and improved the speed and accuracy with which we serve our guests."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Automating Concierge Services to a Fine Level of Detail
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The Concierge Assistant is accessible by The Rittenhouse's front desk, housekeeping, engineering and concierge staffs who have their work cut out for them at a property known for its superb service. "We offer every personal amenity seven days a week, 24 hours each day," said David Benton. "Arranging transportation for guests is an ongoing part of our service that was becoming difficult to track efficiently when we were paper based. With our new Concierge Assistant software if a guest asks for a limo we can immediately show which providers are available for each destination and print out a confirmation and agenda on letterhead. The system is particularly valuable if a guest’s schedule changes because we can implement the change at once and provide a clean updated copy for their itinerary. With a paper-based system this required a great deal of time to write out by hand."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      For the many guests who have an interest in professional sports, the hotel keeps a database of the local teams' websites and schedules in The Concierge Assistant, and often prints out and even emails team game calendars to guests coming to Philadelphia. The Rittenhouse also maintains a record of its hotel guests' preferred eating places, both on property and regionally, and keeps a list of the maitre d's at each establishment to ensure dining arrangements are accurate.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      Condominium Repairs Logged and Resolved Overnight with Concierge Software
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      The Rittenhouse, rising 33 stories above Philadelphia's historic Rittenhouse Square, offers the largest hotel rooms in the city, many with full kitchens, as well as 7/24 room service and a state of the art security system to maintain privacy for guests that include celebrities like Phil Collins, The Beachboys and Bruce Willis. The hotel's tower also holds 160 condominiums that are home to many influential and well-known residents. "Our concierge staff is very capable, as one would expect. Besides serving our hotel guests they work double duty attending to the personal needs of our condominium residents as well. We do not have the marketing muscle of a major franchise, so we depend on our superior attention to detail and word of mouth recommendations by guests who have valued their time with us," Benton explains.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Rittenhouse's signature guest service extends across property to its sales office, housekeeping and engineering departments as well. Tracking events that pertain to specific guests is now automated so information on the function room, outlet or other site a guest may be attending is instantly available from every terminal accessing the property's guest service database. "Since our new concierge software is on our network, staff members in sales or at the front desk can access guest information to confirm appointments or schedules when asked," said Benton. "Our housekeeper is also on the network and able to receive requests for linens or other items for both hotel guests and condominium residents. All requests are timed so management can instantly see how long a request has been outstanding and take additional action as necessary."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Because guest comfort is at the heart of guest service the property's engineering staff maintains a 7/24 team at the hotel to ensure all repair requests from the hotel's guests, and condominium residents, are logged and resolved as quickly as possible. "Our ownership unit residents often need repairs or service on the weekends. When I get into my office on most mornings one of the first things I do is review our overnight repairs, guest requests and any outstanding needs," said Benton. "I use The Concierge Assistant to get a snapshot of the night's activities and look for action items that need to be addressed. In fact, tracking service requests by day gives us an excellent staff forecasting tool."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      "Many hotel technologies detract from personal interaction with guests," said The Rittenhouse's David Benton. "We would only adopt a system that enhances our personalized attention to guests. Our experience is that The Concierge Assistant allows our staff to meet visitors' needs more efficiently and accurately with a wealth of information that benefits our guests. When hosting people that could stay anywhere they like, service is what sets The Rittenhouse apart."
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About The Rittenhouse.
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      Winner of the AAA Five Diamond Super Star award, and the American Academy of Hospitality Sciences, Star Diamond Award, The Rittenhouse is ranked among the "Top Hotels in The World" by Conde Nast and the Official Hotel Guide. The hotel is also featured in Simply the Best magazine as one of the "Top 20 Hotels in the U.S." The hotel's premier location on Rittenhouse Square is in the heart of Philadelphia's most prestigious residential, business, cultural and retail area, only 8 miles from Philadelphia International Airport and a quick 10 blocks from the train station and convention center. The Rittenhouse services include 24-hour room service and concierge service, twice daily maid service, 24-hour security staff and state-of-the-art systems, and seven-day laundry and valet service. The Rittenhouse is a member of The Leading Small Hotels of The World.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsRittenhouseFountainPhoto.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Ritten House Fountain</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>
  <newsItem>
    <id>01</id>
    <visible>true</visible>
    <title>
      The Five-Star Landmark London Applies Automated
      Concierge Technology to Put Polish on Personal Service
    </title>
    <date>2005-01-11T09:48:32.0Z</date>
    <content>
      <![CDATA[<i>]]>
      Les Clefs d'Or member Uses ‘The Concierge Assistant’ to Provide
      Guests with Information on over 900 Restaurants
      and Services in London
      <![CDATA[</i><br /><br />]]>
      London, England – January 11, 2005 – The prestigious Landmark London hotel near Regent’s Park, awarded Best Hotel in London twice in the last three years, has invested in a new guest service software system to automate their already superb concierge experience.  The property’s professional concierge staff uses the new system, named The Concierge Assistanttm from Gold Key Solutions, to track guest preferences, make dining, spa, and other reservations, and refine guest service.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      The Landmark London’s chief concierge, Robert Watson, Les Clefs d'Or member and International VP of Les Clefs d'Or International, who has performed as a concierge for 29 years, said, “This new system will revolutionize the way concierges operate.  From the guest perspective it creates a more professional and efficient service experience.  Visitors are no longer given a handwritten note to verify engagements, but presented a proper printed confirmation and map.  Handwriting is often questioned by guests of different nationalities; now all our directions are uniform.”  Guest preferences are logged in the new system and remembered from visit to visit so regular guests can expect table bookings and other services to be arranged in advance of their arrival at the hotel without making the request each time they visit, strengthening guest recognition standards.
      <![CDATA[<br /><br />]]>
      Where the hotel’s concierges have traditionally relied on a bookshelf of guidebooks, copied flyers and their own knowledge, The Concierge Assistant system was configured by Gold Key Solutions specifically for The Landmark to provide current information on over 900 restaurants and other services in London.  To ensure the highest standard of guest service at the hotel, all concierge staff members access a data trail of assistance for each guest to ensure proper service is provided.  “The system is an excellent tool for a head concierge because he can see what staff are doing, and easily spot the best performers who are working harder and making the most reservations for our guests,” said Robert Watson, The Landmark London’s chief concierge.  “The system shows staff performance side by side, and this helps me spot the need for additional training. I first saw The Concierge Assistant in operation in a 3,500-room hotel in Las Vegas and immediately planned introducing it to The Landmark London.”
      <![CDATA[<br /><br /><b>]]>
      About Landmark London Hotel
      <![CDATA[</b><br /><br />]]>
      With a five-star rating and perfect location in the heart of fashionable Marylebone, The Landmark London, awarded Best Hotel in London 2003, ranks amongst the finest of the UK’s leading luxury hotels. As the glorious modern reincarnation of the Great Central Hotel, The Landmark has its own distinctive style and ambience, combining classic British elegance with a touch of the contemporary. Spacious guest rooms, impeccable service and superb location make it a top destination.
    </content>
    <imageUrl>NewsLandmarkLondon.jpg</imageUrl>
    <imageAltText>Landmark London</imageAltText>
  </newsItem>

</news>